donjohnston.net 2011-11-28

# Don Johnston Incorporated Privacy Statement | Don Johnston Assistive Technology

###### Last updated: Tuesday, 23-August-2011 14:14:45 CDT

Don Johnston Incorporated understands how important it is to keep information about our customers confidential. Information that we gather on our customers is only used internally so that we are able to provide products and services that meet your needs and the needs of your students. We do not sell or offer customer information to third parties. Don Johnston Incorporated is not responsible for customer privacy in relation to sites that link to our site or are listed on our site. 

##### Use of your Customer Personal Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products and services and to respond to your inquiries about our offerings. We may use this information to communicate with you, such as to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter or to contact you about your account with us. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings and hosting of server applications. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

We log IP addresses in order to analyze trends, track statistics within our site and gather broad demographic information. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

##### Security of Customer Personal Information

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. All licensing and contact information is currently held in Illinois, United States. 

##### How You can Access or Correct Information

To access the personally identifiable information that this Don Johnston Incorporated site has collected about you online, you may email your request to [info@donjohnston.com](mailto:info@donjohnston.com)

For any records governed by FERPA, **only** school officials can provide educational records to parents or eligible students. 

##### Use of Student Personal Information

Don Johnston Incorporated’s web based products are designed to comply with the Family Educational Right to Privacy Act. Don Johnston Incorporated will not see, use, or disclose to any third party, unless compelled by law, any personally identifiable student information, educational records, or directory information. Personally identifiable education records are stored solely for use by school officials within the agency or institution that have a legitimate educational interest to access the data. Districts agree to comply with the Family Educational Right to Privacy Act (Buckley Amendment), 20 U.S.C. § 1232g, where applicable. 

##### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the Don Johnston online policy for this site or its implementation you may email us at [info@donjohnston.com](mailto:info@donjohnston.com)

##### Changes to this Statement

Don Johnston Incorporated will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect company and customer feedback. When Don Johnston Incorporated posts changes to this Statement, you will see the last updated date on the top page of this Privacy Statement. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Don Johnston Incorporated will use your personal information, Don Johnston Incorporated will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change.
